<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on A minimal Hugo website</title>
    <link>https://cuteloop.github.io/InfiniteCuteLoop/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on A minimal Hugo website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://cuteloop.github.io/InfiniteCuteLoop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Blog with LaTeX in 15 Minutes</title>
      <link>https://cuteloop.github.io/InfiniteCuteLoop/posts/math-blog-with-latex-support-in-15-min/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cuteloop.github.io/InfiniteCuteLoop/posts/math-blog-with-latex-support-in-15-min/</guid>
      <description>Blog with LaTeX in 15 Minutes Joel Maldonado Welcome to this infinite Cute Loop! In this post, I’m going to share my journey of setting up a Hugo blog with full LaTeX support and deploying it to GitHub Pages—all in just 15 minutes. If you’re curious about how to get your blog up and running quickly, read on!Below is the updated, comprehensive tutorial that incorporates all the details—including creating your GitHub repository, initializing your Hugo site with your final configuration, adding LaTeX support via the custom footer partial, and deploying your site from a dedicated branch (gh‑pages) using ghp‑import.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Plain Markdown Post</title>
      <link>https://cuteloop.github.io/InfiniteCuteLoop/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cuteloop.github.io/InfiniteCuteLoop/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>This sample post is mainly for blogdown users. If you do not use blogdown, you can skip the first section.&#xA;1. Markdown or R Markdown This post is written in plain Markdown (*.md) instead of R Markdown (*.Rmd). The differences include:&#xA;You cannot run any R code in a plain Markdown document, whereas in R Markdown you can embed R code chunks. A plain Markdown post is rendered via Goldmark, while R Markdown is compiled with rmarkdown and Pandoc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://cuteloop.github.io/InfiniteCuteLoop/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cuteloop.github.io/InfiniteCuteLoop/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi there! Welcome to Infinite Cute Loop – a space where my passion for math, research, and creative teaching comes to life. I&amp;rsquo;m a graduate student with a deep love for all things math, and I built this blog to share both academic explorations and playful insights into the world of numbers.&#xA;What you can expect:&#xA;In-depth research and analysis. Creative tutorials and fun math musings. Practical examples to spark inspiration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MATH 112 – Final Exam Practice #3</title>
      <link>https://cuteloop.github.io/InfiniteCuteLoop/posts/math-final-practice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cuteloop.github.io/InfiniteCuteLoop/posts/math-final-practice/</guid>
      <description>How to use this page&#xA;Try each problem first, then expand Hint or Solution as needed. (this is a draft. Currently in the process of checking and reviewing the solutions are correct. I hope It Helps you in your study.)&#xA;Final Exam Practice Exam 3 Answers&#xA;Math 112 final exam resources&#xA;Formulas Provided on the Exam {: #formula-sheet } Quadratics Quadratic Formula Vertex of Parabola \(x = \dfrac{-b \pm \sqrt{b^{2}-4ac}}{2a}\) \(x = -\dfrac{b}{2a}\) Factored Forms</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
